He's dying for followers
Deadstream is a horror, comedy film directed by Vanessa Winter.
A disgraced internet personality attempts to win back his followers
by livestreaming one night alone in a haunted house.
But when he accidentally pisses off a vengeful spirit, his big
comeback event becomes a real-time fight for his life.
Shawn, played by Joseph Winter.
Chrissy / Mildred, played by Melanie Stone.
Corner Man / Cop Corpse, played by Jason K. Wixom.
Hettie, played by Pat Barnett Carr.
Max Loland / Cop, played by Marty Collins.
Latin Professor, played by Perla Lacayo.
Deadstream is a 2022 American supernatural horror comedy film directed, written, produced and edited by wife and husband
Vanessa and Joseph Winter in their directorial debut, with Joseph also acting as lead actor and soundtrack composer.
The plot follows a disgraced content creator attempting to resurrect his career by livestreaming himself spending the
night in a notorious haunted house; the film uses a found footage format, displaying the livestream itself.
Deadstream had its world premiere at South by Southwest on March 11, 2022, and was released
in the United States on October 6, 2022, by Shudder to positive reviews.
The film explores themes of haunted house, ghost, found
footage, urbex, social media influencer.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.